ludicrous.net 2000-12-08

# Ludicrous.net - a page that is something to laugh at!!!

**Ludicrous.net Privacy Policy**

Ludicrous.net is committed to responsible management of consumer information and abides by all rules, both ethical and legal, with respect to the use of consumer information. We strictly adhere to all industry guidelines, and are continuously monitoring and enhancing how we manage the use and security of consumer information to uphold your rights. 

_Personal_

> Ludicrous.net will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (name, address, telephone number, email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it.
> 
> If you do submit your email addresses online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new services or site updates. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by responding the to removal portion of the emails.
> 
> If you have already submitted this information and would like for us to remove it from our files, please contact us at the email or phone listed at the bottom of this Statement. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files.

_Non-personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically_

> For each visitor to www.ludicrous.net, our Web server automatically recognizes your domain, the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our site. This non-personally identifiable information is collected automatically, used for internal review, then discarded.
> 
> Advertisements shown on Ludicrous.net may use cookies to help prevent you from seeing the same ad repeatedly. This information is held by the advertisers and is not available to us.
> 
> Ludicrous.net works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Burst manages the privacy information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to [their web site](http://www.burstmedia.com/)

Return to top.

**Who to Contact**

Please e-mail questions or requests for more information about Ludicrous.net's privacy policies and initiatives to [jokemaster@ludicrous.net](mailto:jokemaster@ludicrous.net?subject=Privacy%20Inquiries).

Any consumer may request removal of his or her name from Ludicrous.net's email database by sending e-mail to [jokemaster@ludicrous.net](mailto:jokemaster@ludicrous.net?subject=Email%20List%20Removal). You must provide your name and e-mail address. We will use reasonable efforts to delete this information from our existing files.

**Consumers' Privacy Rights**

Ludicrous.net holds the consumer relationship in the highest regard and pledges:

  1. To insure that consumers have the ultimate right to control dissemination of their personal information. We support the self-regulation efforts of the direct marketing industry and believe this action is the best way to protect consumer privacy. We support legislation and regulatory efforts, which introduce fair, workable guidelines that protect the privacy of consumers. We will work to ensure that any such guidelines are consistent with and complement established self-regulatory measures, and that they allow the consumer to continue receiving the benefits that sophisticated marketing techniques can provide.
  2. To respond quickly to questions about the accuracy of information we process for our visitors. We appreciate the fact that inaccurate data can have a negative impact upon consumers. If a data error is called to our attention, we will use our best efforts to determine the source of the error and to notify the responsible party and update our records. If the error is in data, which originates with us, we will promptly correct it.
  3. To monitor privacy issues and assure that any changes in legislation or industry standards regarding privacy issues are reflected in our Privacy Policy. Ludicrous.net does its best to stay up to date about the law, industry standards or our Privacy Policy.
  4. To maintain strict data security systems that ensure specific individual information will not be made available to any unauthorized person. Access is only allowed by authorized personnel.
